A Guide to the University of Connecticut, Governmental Relations Office Records 2015.0169
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
University of Connecticut, Governmental Relations Office Records
1983-2002
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
2015.0169
4 Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
Documentation of the activities of the office of Governmental Relations. Materials in the collection shows the connection between the University of Connecticut and the local, state, and national governements and how it impacts the university.
University of Connecticut. Governmental Relations Office
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1981-1999
  - Correspondence (invitation to GHW Bush to speak at Commencement), 1997 (Box 1)
  - History of UConn, Evan Hill (1981 Factbook) (Box 1)
  - Lowell Weicker, Governor, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Organization chart, undated (Box 2)
  - Pfizer, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - President Hartley's Five Year report, 1990-1995 (Box 2)
  - Proposed New Marine Sciences and Technology Center (framed), AVP, 1994 March (Oversize OS)
  - Record of Decision Connecticut Technology Park Access Road, 1988 May (Box 1)
  - S. Res 107, 1995 April 6 (Oversize OS)
  - Technology Quadrant Pre-Design Study, Technical report 1, 1990 August 1 (Box 1)
  - Tech Transfer, 1997 (Box 1)
  - UCEPI, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - UCEPI, 1985-1992 (Box 1)
  - UCEPI--Concept Master Plan, 1983 August 25 (Box 1)
  - UCEPI Long Range Planning Discussion, 1992 August 11 (Box 1)
  - UCEPI (Information packet), undated (Box 1)
  - UCEPI/UConn Tech Park, 1996 (Box 1)
- Series II: Awards and Commendations, undated, 1998, 2002
  - All-American Candidates (Sales, Hamilton, Williams), undated (Box 2)
  - Football signees, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Freshman of the Year candidate (Abrosimova), undated (Box 2)
  - Official citations awarded to students, 2002 (Oversize OS)
- Series III: Newspapers, Magazines, and Periodicals, 1993-2004
  - Clippings, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 2004 (Box 1)
  - The Daily Campus, 1995 September 11 - 15 (Box 2)
  - Sports Illustrated--MBB, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Sports Illustrated-WBB, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Traditions, 1995 Summer (Box 2)
  - Traditions, 1995 Fall (Box 2)
- Series IV: Photographs and Multimedia, undated, 1992-2000
  - Legislators Basketball game photograhs, undated (Box 1, Box 2)
  - Photograph, Bill Clinton (signed) holding sweatshirt, 1992 September 24 (Box 1)
  - Photographs (Golf, Clinton), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph (framed) of Governor Rowland and Jonathan Husky (mascot), Support UConn 2000, undated (Oversize OS)
  - Photographs of students with Governor Rowland, Scott Brohinsky and Mark Emmert, undated (Box 1)
  - Team photograph--Football, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Team photograph--WBB, 1995 (Box 2)
  - VHS tapes
    - Precision Manufacturing Center, Paretnerships for manufacturing progress, undated (Box 2)
    - Chris Dodd & Birch Bayh--WBB--Title IX (2 copies), 2004 January 19 (Box 2)
    - UConn Outreach: Meet the Honorable Jonathan Pelto, 1987 November 17 (Box 2)
    - Governor John Rowland, Interview for Campaign UConn, 2001 September 4 (Box 2)
    - The NEMO Project, Helping Communities balance growth and natural resources, 2001 Winter (Box 2)
    - The University of Connecticut, "The Spirit", undated (Box 2)
    - Charles and Augustus Storrs Award, 2002 November 6 (Box 2)